I'm not in the mood.
Is it almost time for Sword Hazard?
No.
If I watch anime now to escape,
there's no way I can focus on my studies.
The exam is tomorrow.
It's starting.
Have I lost my perseverance?
I've forgotten...
how to work hard.
I'll do my best.
At least, I can't let Alya
be dragged down by my evaluation.
What?
Alya?
Hello?
Good evening, Kuze.
Good evening.
What's the matter?
It's nothing important.
What is it?
Do you suddenly want to hear my voice?
Can't I?
What was that sound?
Nothing.
So, what's up?
Well, didn't you say that studying alone
makes you want to slack off?
So I called to ask how it's going.
Well, it's true that
I'm not motivated at all.
How do you stay motivated
at a time like this?
I don't do it on purpose.
After all, I've never lost my motivation.
So I don't know how.
Seriously? Man, you're amazing.
If you're not motivated,
do you want to make a bet?
A bet?
What's your goal this time?
Let's just say I want to be
in the top 30 of our grade.
That's high.
All right.
If you can achieve that goal,
I'll grant you any wish.
Did you just say any wish?
But within your conscience.
Do you want to take the bet?
What if I can't achieve it?
Of course, you'll have to grant me a wish.
I'm pretty interested in that too.
Kuze?
It's nothing.
I didn't have any masochist thoughts
about wanting
to be ordered around just now.
Name.
What?
This is a hint.
No, I don't understand Russian.
I know.
It's a deal then, okay?
Okay, I'm game.
I'll make you regret making this bet.
Yeah, good luck with that.
Your ignoring skills have improved.
Your older brother feels a little lonely.
When did you become my brother?
Aren't we the same age?
Isn't your birthday on November 7th?
Yes, it is.
How do you know that?
Didn't you tell me in class
when you transferred here?
Well, that's not important.
My birthday is on April 9th.
I'm already 16 years old.
Anyway, thank you for calling me, Alya.
See you tomorrow.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
I didn't think she'd notice
that I wasn't motivated.
Is this the so-called telepathy?
I definitely can't tell him
that I got scared
and called him out of fear.
What the heck?
If he had told me when his birthday was,
I could've at least wished him
a happy birthday.
He clearly said
that we were friends.
Kuze is such an idiot.
FIVE DAYS LATER
The exams are over!
Alya, good job on the exams.
Yeah, you too.
So um...
Do you have any plans after school?
No, I don't.
Then, do you want to go home together?
I want to discuss
the closing ceremony with you.
Sure.
That's strange.
Ever since our last phone call,
Alya stopped using Russian
to hide her feelings.
So?
Aren't we going to talk
about the closing ceremony speech?
That's true.
But I have a question first.
Since exam week,
don't you think
you've been acting strangely?
I thought I didn't show it.
No, it's true that you hardly
showed it in your attitude.
But I noticed it.
That means you're
quite concerned about me.
Even though it's exam week.
Of course I'm concerned.
You're my precious partner after all.
If that's the case, why...
Birthday.
What?
Why didn't you invite me
to your birthday party?
Birthday party?
I didn't have such a party.
Where did you hear that?
It's impossible that you
didn't have a birthday party.
Could it be that the people in Russia
usually have birthday parties?
Yes.
Don't they do that in Japan?
I haven't had a birthday party
since I was in elementary school.
I see.
Do you want to celebrate
my birthday that badly?
It's because in Russia,
not sharing your birthday
means "I won't be
on good terms with you this year."
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'll take your word for it.
You're annoying!
Well then, will you celebrate my birthday?
What?
It's been three months,
but I want to get along
with you this year too.
After this, I'll throw
a belated birthday party.
Please come.
What are you talking about?
Kuze.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's so hot.
But it's better than wearing
the long-sleeved uniform at school.
You're right.
But didn't the President suggest
that we change our summer uniforms
to short-sleeved ones?
That's right.
But even if that happens,
it will probably
have to wait until next year.
That's crazy.
Passers-by are doing a double-take.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just feel like everyone
is looking at you.
No point bothering about it.
This is the fate of a beauty.
If you go out alone,
won't you get hit on like crazy?
Yes.
I get hit on a lot on my days off.
I knew it.
How do you deal with them?
Until they give up,
I just have to keep talking
to them in Russian.
I see.
That's great.
I thought she'd beat them back
with a sharp tongue and violence.
Are you thinking
of something rude right now?
No, not at all.
I'm just glad you didn't fall
for their bad pickup techniques.
Oh my, is this so-called possessiveness?
You're acting like my boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
When guys are on a date,
they tend to act like
a boyfriend, even a little.
Is that so?
A date...
You're right.
This is my first time.
Right.
She must've meant
that it's her first date with me.
For a pretty girl like her,
there's no way
it's her first time going out on a date.
AGED BEEF CLAN CONTINUES
-Is this the place?
-Yes.
It's a fancy restaurant at night.
But during lunchtime,
you can get a variety of meat
at a reasonable price.
I have good taste in restaurants, don't I?
-The...
-The food here is indeed delicious.
I've been here with my family before.
I remember that the venison
is especially delicious.
Is that so?
Well...
Well then,
I'll briefly explain the closing ceremony.
Okay.
First, the presidential candidates
will talk about
their ideals for the election.
Then, the partner will explain
why they want him or her
to be the president.
And then, this is the important part.
Actually, this event
doesn't have voting,
but it has a similar process.
What?
After each pair's speech,
the audience will only applaud
the pair they want to root for.
So, is it possible for the venue
to go silent without any applause at all?
That's right.
To be honest,
I don't think we'll get the same applause
as Yuki in our current state.
That's why
our goal is to keep the gap from widening.
No need to focus on winning.
Isn't that too negative?
It's my judgment after calmly assessing
the power gap between us and our enemies.
You're right. I understand.
One more thing.
During the speech,
let's do our best to go first.
Going first will set the bar for the rest.
So there'll be fewer applause
no matter what.
Even if we're left behind,
we can find a way to save face.
Don't make that face.
But if we can do whatever it takes,
there are other ways.
Like what?
Like attacking Yuki
and Ayano's mental state.
But this kind of rough play
isn't your style, is it?
That's true.
Things would be different
if the other party did it first.
But I don't think
they would go that far.
It's not like they're Miyamae.
-What's that...
-Thank you for waiting.
Well, anyway, let's consider this
a commemoration of my birthday.
Cheers!
Cheers.
This is delicious.
Yes.
The rumor about Miyamae.
Was it your idea, Kuze?
I planted some shills in the audience.
Sayacchi found out about it.
Something like that.
No.
Miyamae came up with that on her own
and spread the rumor herself.
I see.
The rumor about Taniyama was put to rest,
but the result of the general meeting
also became somewhat ambiguous.
I'm sorry.
There must have been a better way.
No, it's fine.
After all, I didn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything either.
I have no right to criticize this result.
So thank you, Kuze.
Thank you for helping me.
Don't mention it.
Oh, my. What's wrong?
Are you blushing?
Shut up.
How cute.
Hey!
She's straight up saying it
in Japanese now!
Here, this is my thanks.
She's so full of herself.
She thinks I'm flustered,
so she seized the chance to attack.
Did you forget this is why
you couldn't use the spoon last time?
Thank you. It was delicious.
Really?
What?
She didn't waver at all!
Alya is leading me by the nose today.
I'm full.
Thank you for the meal.
-Well then, it's time for your present.
-What?
Here, please take it.
You even prepared a present for me?
Thank you.
It seems to be a very tasteful mug.
I know, right?
Thank you. I'll cherish it.
Yes, you must.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
For tableware items,
couples usually buy them
in pairs, don't they?
Oh, my. You know your stuff.
This is a pair too, of course.
I've already used mine at home.
Seriously?
If I said that, what would you do?
Somehow,
I can't beat her at all today.
While we wait for
the parent-teacher conference,
I'd like to discuss
the summer uniforms with everyone.
Well then, shall I make some tea?
Yes, please.
Ayano, you don't have to get up.
Kuze, is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
So President,
any progress on summer uniform changes?
Just between you and me,
but after summer break,
we should be able to use the new uniforms.
What? Really?
Yes.
I'm planning to announce it
as a surprise at the closing ceremony.
That's wonderful.
I also love this uniform,
but it's too hot for this season.
So I appreciate it!
Thank you.
But the reason this project was approved
is all thanks to you, Chisaki.
Not at all.
It's the result of your patience
in negotiating, Touya.
Chisaki.
Touya.
How do they enter
their own world of two so naturally?
Here you go. Thank you for waiting.
Here, please enjoy.
Thank you, Masha.
Is she still upset
about the hypnosis incident?
My family must be here.
I'm off to the parent-teacher conference.
Good luck.
I'll clean up first.
I'll help.
Thank you then.
Hey, Masha.
Well,
I'm sorry.
I hypnotized you last time.
No, it's okay.
I'm the one who started it, after all.
Well, the thing is,
I didn't get to ask you back then.
When I was hypnotized,
did I do anything to you?
Well...
You held me and Alya in your arms
and kept stroking our heads.
What?
Is that all?
Yes, that's about it.
I see. That's good.
By the way,
did you... see that?
Kuze, you're a pervert.
I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
So Masha could get angry
at a time like this.
But she's not scary at all.
She's actually really cute.
Kuze?
Yes!
Have you been seriously repenting?
What are you doing?
A punishment, of course.
Listen carefully.
Don't make girls embarrassed.
Yes.
Good.
I think my mom is here.
Please go ahead.
I'll take care of the rest.
Well then, can I count on you?
All right, take care.
Sarashina and Alya have left too.
I see.
We're finally alone.
I'll wait for Grandpa too.
Hey, wait!
Why are you ignoring me?
No!
You're the one who shouldn't
treat Ayano like she's invisible!
That's cold.
It's been a while
since we talked as siblings, right?
Indeed, now that you mention it.
But you're having so much fun with Alya
so maybe you don't really care.
That's not true... What?
Poor me. I'm so lonely.
I see. You're so lonely?
Anyway, get off the table.
So,
give me some love!
Hey, your mood changes way too fast!
What's wrong? Get over here quickly.
Does it have to be here?
Yes.
I want you to give me some love
right here, right now,
Masachika.
I... get it.
All right, come here.
I think I'll pass!
Just kidding.
You're so cool!
Grandpa's here.
Grandpa?
Masachika, you're here.
Why are you wearing a white suit?
What? Don't I look cool?
Didn't I tell you only narcissists
and foreign mafia wear this kind of stuff?
I see.
Is it because this is missing?
Look, don't I look handsome?
You look more like a mobster!
I'm sure you were influenced
by a movie or something.
By the way, where did you get that outfit?
I bought it with my meager pension
just for today.
Go and get scolded by Grandma.
Is Kyoutarou still busy?
Yeah.
I heard he joined
the British Embassy this year.
Everything must be hard for him.
But he should at least attend
the parent-teacher conference.
He said he can't make it.
Masachika, you're so kind.
Stop it.
We'll take our leave.
Thank you for your time.
Shoot!
-Kuze...
-The Miracle of Eastern Europe!
Why don't you shut up?
I'm sorry, Alya.
This is my grandpa.
He has a strong admiration for Russia.
I see.
Little girl, what is your name?
I told you to stop!
What a very energetic grandpa.
Are you Kuze?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Are you Alisa's mother?
Oh, my. You are so polite.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Alisa's mother, Akemi Kujou.
I've heard a lot about you
from my daughter.
I hope she didn't say
anything bad about me.
She always talks about you happily.
Is that so?
Little girl.
Do you want to be my granddaughter?
What?
Hey, Grandpa!
What do you think?
Would you like to marry my Masachika?
Please shut up now!
So, what do you think of her?
I told you to shut up.
So,
Alya, are you going to marry Kuze?
Mom, don't say that.
Well then, we'll be going now.
Goodbye.
Well then,
about that Ms. Alisa...
Let's stop talking about that.
Yumi, it's been a while.
It's been a while,
sir.